Chapter 0: Prologue

On a sunny morning, Silvermoon City bathed in a warm sunlight, creating a lazy atmosphere inside the only main city within the China servers of < >. As the morning slowly rolled over, more and more players started to come online. Everyone, both male and female, were chattering about bosses and equipments, everyone seemed abnormally busy.

At the center of the city, a majestic hall echoed the sweet rings of bells throughout the city.

Holy Cathedral, the location where only players with the title of God could come online. All of the members of the Holy Cathedral were a source of pride and respect for all players. However, the daunting obstacles barred most, almost all players from joining the Holy Cathedral. In fact, only 7 players in the China servers were a member of the Holy Cathedral. All of the members had the title of God!

Sha sha…

FalLi Leaves, under the influence of wind, slowly rolled onto the stairs of Holy Cathedral. Not far from the steps, a young man dressed in full armor walked leisurely towards the hall. Traces of loneliness were seeping out from under the charming face of the man, his eyes revealed an elusive sorrow, with light flame surrounding his armor, a large cloak swaying in the wind, and an ID which everyone was familiar with—–

[Ling Mu Yu] LV-255
Title: War God
Affiliation: Silvermoon City
Guild : Heroes Guild
Position: Guild Leader
World ranking: 1

……

“It’s still as quiet like before?”

Ling Mu Yu raised his head and looked at the World Tree, located in the middle of Holy Cathedral. He had brought this World Tree from the North a long time ago, and with the years, the tree had finally blossomed. In fact, his title of War God, which allowed him to stand side by side with the Magic God, Fang Ge Xue at the apex of , was due to this tree.

“It’s about time to end.”

Evidently he had something gnawing at him, and walked out of the Holy Cathedral.

Outside of the Holy Cathedral, there were countless players running around. Alone, Ling Mu Yu slowly walked next to the city’s walls.

While walking, suddenly he felt a pat on his shoulders, which was followed by an affectionate hug around his shoulders. Without any doubt, there was only a person who dared to do this in Silver City – Li Le, Ling Mu Yu’s best friend who grew up with him since childhood. Unfortunately, due to circumstances, Li Le traveled abroad and couldn’t stay with Ling Mu Yu. But as luck would have it, they played the game together all the time, and he was the Guild’s deputy chief.

“Ah Le?”

Ling Mu Yu turned his head and smiled, saying, “Why are you such a sneaky bastard?”

Li Le laughed, “Ah Yu, I saw that you’re unhappy. What’s wrong? Why do you as if your dad just died? But I thought I saw him healthy and well last time and shouldn’t you be happy if he’s dead?.”

Li Le had always been living life relaxed, as if he had no worries at all. Ling Mu Yu envied him for his freedom.

“I’ve made my decision. I think it’s time for me to leave.” Ling Mu Yu softly said as if he wasn’t sure of his words.

“What?”

Li Le was taken aback by this, “Ah Yu, you’re not joking right? You just obtained the title War God, and you’re planning to leave already? Or…. Is it because of your father?”

Ling Mu Yu could only smile helpless, “Yup, my father gave me an ultimatum, I must leave the game, and help him in family matters. I promised him earlier, that I would reach the top in this game within 2 years. Now that I’ve done it, it’s about time to fulfill my promise, and start to do things that I’m supposed to be doing. Honestly….. I’m ready to stop playing yet!”

Li Le laughed loudly, as if there was nothing funnier than this situation, and patted on Ling Mu Yu’s shoulders, said, “The War God, Ling Mu Yu, also the second son of the president of Long Kan Company, can’t believe you have such a tough life when your worth over 100 Billion. Seems like not everything is good for rich people, but…… Have you really decided?”

“Yup.”

Ling Mu Yu nod


Chapter 1: Seven Luminary Demon King
A body was falling downwards into a tunnel of darkness at full speed. After God knows how long, with a brilliant flash of light, Lin Mu Yu no longer suffered from the splitting pain in his body, instead, he was engulfed by a burning sensation.

P-tongg!

He fell onto a relatively soft surface. But when he extended his hand, he could feel nothing but heat.

“Eh? What is this place? It’s so d*mn hot, I feel like I’m a roasted duck in an oven!”

When he opened his eyes, Lin Mu Yu was greeted with a terrifying sight. Surrounded by streams of boiling lava, he sat amidst a sea of fire. He was fortunate that he had landed on a rock protruding from the lava.

Didn’t I just disconnect from ? But where the hell is this…This is definitely doesn’t seem like my living room…

…

He sat there, stunned. Suddenly, he was engulfed in a suffocating atmosphere. From above him came an insidious voice. “Hehe, Seven Luminaries Demon King, you call yourself a demon emperor, but you’ve never thought you’d fall to where you are today, no?”

An old man wearing a long green robe stood on a horoscope of stars in the air above him. He was flying! With every step he took, a spectrum of rainbow stars manifested beneath his feet. It was an incredibly beautiful sight. There was no mistake that he was a Master!

The Master looked smugly at the sea of lava before his expression suddenly changed to one of extreme hatred.

“When you single-handedly murdered more than a thousand of us, you never thought this day would come, did you? You would never have expected that I would gather twenty four God Masters and a hundred Sacred Masters to spend a century hunting you down!”

Against the raven-black sky, lights flashed one after another. Within a blink of an eye, almost two hundred Masters appeared in the sky, forming an iron wall. Each of them had a suffocating killing intent in their faces. Even the atmosphere they emitted was enough to choke Lin Mu Yu. Perhaps because of their overwhelming strength, they completely overlooked Lin Mu Yu. Or perhaps…it was because Lin Mu Yu did not even amount to a speck of dust compared to them so that they did not bother paying attention to him.

Lin Mu Yu was completely dumbfounded. Was this a movie? It has got to be a dream. A dream! I won’t be fooled. As long as I pinch myself, I’ll definitely wake up.

Without reservation, he pinches himself. Aiyo, the pain! But when he lifted his head, the Masters were still there.

Was this not a dream?

…

It was at that moment that the sea of lava started seething, forming countless huge waves. Suddenly, the lava culminated into a titanic wave! At the crest of the wave, a person stood proudly. It was a man who wore a jet-black robe. He appeared around thirty and was unbelievably handsome. With a contemptuous yet furious expression, he yells, “Qin Yi, you despicable villain! You slaughtered your way into the seventeenth level of hell when I was sleeping. Even if you destroyed my Magic Veins, do you really think these mere hundreds of people before me can resist the power of my Seven Luminaries?”

He raised his palm slowly with a war-like expression on his face. The surrounding seas of fire surged violently.

With a face of concentration, Qin Yi bellows, “Righteous friends, the opportunity to walk the right path has appeared! Let us combine our power and destroy the Seven Luminaries Demon King to restore peace to all the lands!”

“Yes!”

The surrounding people yelled as one as they burst into action one after another, each brandishing their swords. Immediately, the sky lit up with streaks of colour, enough to dazzle Lin Mu Yu.

But even as the Masters’ killing intent exploded, it was not fast enough to match that of the Seven Luminaries Demon King.

Whooosh!

As the demon king raises his palm to the heavens, numerous pillars of lava shoot upwards. With a resolute expression, he roars:



The great waves of Hellfire ascended like sharp blades, frightening Li
